Enjoy Simple English 森崎ウィンです
毎週火曜日は短編のショートコメディ コメディスケッチです
今日お届けするのは A Time Bomb and Smolier Test
次元爆弾とソムリエのテストの2本です
次元爆弾時間内に解除できるのか
そしてマリコはソムリエとして そのお店の試験を合格できるのか
早速聞いてみましょう
タイムボム
ボムが爆発するまで何分か残っているのか教えてくれる?
気をつけなければなりませんが、50%のチャンスで正解することができます。
それは高いパーセンテージです。
残念ながら、33%まで下がっています。
何を意味しているのですか?
後ろにグリーンワイヤーがあるのを見つけたのです。
ああ、いいえ。でも、3つのチャンスはまだあります。
あ、あ、あ、あ、あ、25%まで下がっているようです。
No, don't tell me you found another one
Yes, a yellow wire
Oh no, we're running out of time
Just choose one and cut it
I can't
Yes, you can
I know you can
But I can't
Why not?
I don't have any wire cutters
I only have two seconds left!
No!
Huh?
What just happened?
The good news is that I'm OK.
The bad news is that I think it was just an alarm clock.
Sorry to waste your time.
Sommelier Test
Thank you for coming today. I chose two wines. Our sommelier Chad will be giving you the test.
Thank you.
Let's start your test, Mariko. Please tell me about wine A.
Okay. The wine is light pink. The smell is not too strong and it reminds me of home. It's very calming.
give me a little more detail please
it smells like mushrooms in autumn
it has a light flavor but it becomes more complex
alright now how about wine b
of course
oh um the color smell and
ワインAよりも味は同じだよ
嘘か?
人々はワインの違いを伝えることを信じる
でも同じだよ
違いはない
見てみよう
ワインAは魚に良い
ワインBは肉に良い
You are not good enough for our restaurant. You can go now.
Wait, don't go.
Mariko, you passed the test.
Wine A and Wine B are the same wine.
What? That can't be true.
But it is.
Thank you for working with us, until now.
But I think we have found a new sommelier.
スモーリエ
発音難しいですね
これは要チェックでございます
次元爆弾
もうなくなる寸前に切る道具がないって
もうどういうことだっていう
そして今日のポイント
1 in 3
3回に1回ということですね
これはもう使えると思います
ぜひぜひ使ってみてください
それではSee you tomorrow